Al Amin Bin Ahmad

Full Stack Developer with Django

Address Katsina, Nigeria 820101

Phone: 07067156212

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single

L.G.A: Batagarawa

D.O.B: 20th OCT, 2001

G-mail alaminbinahmad78@gmail.com

GitHub https://github.com/Bin02-Dv

Linked In https://www.linkedin.com/in/al-amin-

bin-ahmad-2933b82a7/

My Portfolio site

https://binportfoliomark2.onrender.com

I'm a Python developer using Python development processes by exploiting open-source web frameworks. Specializes in applying Django to complex database assets with strong web presences. Comfortable taking over ongoing administration processes or designing customized administration models.

Technical Profile/Skills

- Python
- o SQL
- Mango DB
- o HTML5
- JavaScript
- Ajax/Json
- jQuery
- o CSS3
- o Git/GitHub
- Bootstrap
- o Linux
- o Burp suite
- Django
- Rest API

Work History

2021-2023 Full Stack Developer at Proxy Software Systems

2023-Current Full Stack Developer at Lumilab Tech Service

Education

2021-11 - 2022-02 High School Diploma

Katsina State Institute of Technology and Management (KSITM) - Abba Musa Rimi Way, Ring Rd, Katsina

Software

Web app development

Languages

Hausa Language

English Language

Certifications

2022 – 02	Certified – National Diploma in Computer Software Engineering
2022-02	Certified - Web Development, Proxy Software Systems
2023-07	Certified - Basics of Machine Learning, Great Learning
2023-16	Certified – Ethical Hacking, A-I Online Vocational Training Institute

Interests

I have interest in Artificial Intelligence, Web Development, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, APIs (Development and Integration) and Ethical Hacking.

Projects – Software (Student projects)

- Attendance Management System
- Hospital Management System
- Student Result Prediction using Data mining
- Blood Banking Management System
- Computerized Chamber Management System
- Medical Duties Scheduling System
- Simple Word Processor, etc

Projects – Software (My projects)

- Human Resources and Payroll System
- Software Developer Salary Predictor
- Inventory Management System
- Result Processing System, etc

Projects - APIs

- Authentication APIs
- VTU APIs
- Payment Getaway API, etc

Programming

I started learning programming when I was 18-year-old, and I jump in to programming because, I have something I want to achieve in my life.